If the red string of fate
ties two people together,
what color string connects
two unrequited lovers?
"That stuff doesn't exist," you say?
Of course it does.
Beautiful Meanings
Behind Flowers
How else could two people
have such a strong bond
but be destined to be apart?
I bet it's a string with a lame color.
Like the color of my eyes right now.
I'm sure of it.
Flowers that Bloom Along
the Path of Dreams
I really hate the summer.
I sweat way too much.
And guys stare more.
We don't have band practice today but...
I bet Yu-kun doesn't want any visitors.
Rion! Got a minute?
Can you take Kureha's gift
to the Makishimas?
But it's my day off!
Can't Onee-chan take it?
Looks like she's already left.
What?
You know how restless she gets.
Thanks, Rion.
You're way too soft on Onee-chan.
It's done! Himari-chan's going to Tokyo!
Rin-chan's sure to win now!
That lame perfectionist's got nothing on me!
Take that, you loser!
He's weirdly energetic, it's creepy.
You're home for a change?
I figured you'd be out with girls.
I'm in a good mood. Don't burst my bubble.
What's the visit for?
Oh, Kureha-san's gift.
I'll give it to the others later.
What's your problem?
Go ahead and say it.
Onee-chan's trying to take Hii-chan away.
She seems pretty set on her.
But this is your chance, isn't it?
That's not fair, though.
You're still trying to play nice?
Himari-chan was the one
who tried to one-up you.
Anything's fair game.
I mean sure, but...
Shii-kun, can you stop her?
No can do.
I've pulled all these strings
to help you win.
I can't put all my hard work to wast—
I bet Onee-chan would be impressed
if you can outsmart her.
Like with tennis.
Going to nationals is just to make
Onee-chan admit you're above Hibari-san.
Not to mention you only approached Yu-kun
because he was Hibari-san's favorite.
And now look at you, you're actual friends.
Want me to keep going?
Fine! I get it!
You're right.
Not that I care one bit about
that cruel woman!
But it would feel nice
to beat her at her own game.
You sure, though?
You might essentially be handing
the win to Himari-chan!
Fine with me!
I don't want to win like this anyways.
You sisters are both so stubborn.
Fine, but after this,
I'm not helping you anymore.
Got that?
I never asked you for help. Besides...
I'm only letting Himari-chan borrow Yu-kun.
In the end, I'll be the winner!
Good grief.
I almost feel bad for Himari-chan for having
a lifelong rival with such nerves of steel.
Hi, there.
What an unexpected caller.
A favor?
I'll be all alone at the
Gardening Club until graduation.
It might even be that way
until I open my own store.
Or even for the rest of my life.
Himari may never come back.
If it comes to that, would
I even want to open a store?
I'd spend ten, twenty years living
an ordinary life without her.
Dammit!
Why am I being so negative?!
Everything will be fine!
I trust Himari. I'll work hard, too!
You look as miserable as ever.
Isn't it Himari-chan's job to water
the flowers in the morning?
She's leaving for Tokyo today.
What time does the train leave?
Around noon, I think.
Then we've got some time.
Let's have a chat.
Huh?
You're going too, aren't you?
This might be our last chance
to talk face-to-face.
Why would I go to Tokyo?
Oh?
Weren't you all worked up
about following her back in May?
You've already decided
to give up accessories once.
How's it different
the second or third time?
This situation's totally different.
Is it? How so?
Himari wants to model for my accessories.
How could I stop her?
How lame.
That's how I know you're stupid.
What do you—
What's so wrong about
devoting your life to a woman?
You don't need your own store
to make accessories.
You don't have to be an artist,
you can work a normal job
and be with the woman you love.
Is that such a bad life?
But you can't make that choice.
Why? Because you're afraid of going
back to your old, boring self.
You're afraid of being surrounded
by people who look down on you.
Let me be brutally honest.
You don't actually love Himari-chan.
You're just taking advantage of her.
You spent two years as her best friend
only because that's what she wanted.
Now that she wants romance,
you're playing your part.
It's all for your own convenience.
You wouldn't care whichever way.
What the hell would you know?
You—!
You have no clue
what we mean to each other!
I... I love Himari!
Even if she didn't help my dream!
Even if she didn't protect me!
I've already decided to be with Himari!
Great. You know where you stand.
Now there's only one thing to do.
I played it close, he almost hit me.
It's not easy having to live
without your number one girl like me.
That's right. It was her all along.
I just wanted her eyes on me.
Whoa, bro.
You okay?
Yu!
That's all I needed!
I'm such a backstabber.
I pretended to support Enocchi.
Only to kiss Yu behind her back.
But... I've never liked someone so much
that none of that even mattered.
On my way!
I'm by the station entrance.
Oops, sorry. Stuck in traffic.
I hope she doesn't show up.
Snap out of it. You've made up your mind.
I was just unlucky.
Kureha-san said my looks were my talent.
That made me happy.
After all, I didn't think
I was good for anything.
Maybe, just maybe, my looks could help Yu.
Still, if I think about
what's most important to me,
it's the time I spend with Yu.
And now, I can't have that anymore.
If that's how it is, I don't want to
be the prettiest girl in the world.
I don't even want these fairy-like eyes.
Or any friends. Or family.
I just wish I were born
as someone loved by Yu.
Hii-chan.
E-Enocchi!
You came to see me off?
You're too nice!
Not like that idiot who left me on read.
I'm not here for that.
I just wanted to say thanks.
Say thanks?
Hii-chan, you threw the match.
So thanks!
Y-You're mad I kissed Yu, huh?
That was nothing, it was—
You're still trying to play the good girl?
It's been obvious the entire time.
There's no use glossing it over.
Are your dreams more important
than your true feelings?
O-Of course they are!
You know how hard Yu's worked for it!
Sure I do.
It would be a huge plus
for the store one day.
Besides, modeling
isn't something anyone can do.
But why do it if you don't want to?
Then why don't you go instead!
Okay!
I'll go.
I'm not sure if I'm cut out for it,
but I'll do it for you and Yu-kun.
B-But...
So give me Yu-kun in return.
I'll let you borrow him
until he opens his store.
But when I come home, give him to me.
You don't mind, right?
Let's pinky promise!
No?
You can still be best friends.
It's okay.
I'm sure you'll be able to
find someone just like him!
No, that's not it.
I wasn't the one who found Yu.
Yu was the one who discovered me.
There's no doing that again.
See, you're trying too hard.
You've always been like that.
Even though you steal everything you want,
you've never been able to
say what you want most.
I don't wanna!
I hate it!
I don't really wanna go!
There, there. I know.
But this was all my fault.
I have to make up for it somehow.
And what if Yu's better off without me?
Honestly, I wonder about that too.
You always stir up trouble
and involve everyone around you.
Are you trying to kill me or what?
You know what I noticed?
You two are both so focused on
how to make your dreams come true.
What do you mean?
Does it have to be that complicated?
Like my mom.
Making sweets was initially just a hobby.
She only opened her own store recently.
Really?
Having a dream is nice, but you
can't lose sight of the present.
Opening a store isn't everything.
But it might be for Yu.
You think so?
Is the store the most
important thing to Yu-kun?
Or is it—
Himari!
Yu!
See?
What are you doing here?
Please don't go!
I can't choose between
my dream and romance.
I'm not even sure which is the right answer.
But I do know that you don't
actually want to go to Tokyo!
But this is the only way I can help.
That's not true.
And you don't need to help me.
You don't need to do anything.
We don't need a purpose to be together.
That's not what this is about!
I was so afraid to lose the one
person who understands my passion.
I was too afraid to lose you!
That's why I was so fixated
on what we could do for each other.
But all I ever wanted was for you to see me!
If you're doing this for me,
don't sacrifice yourself!
There's no having fun without you around.
Like the best friends we've always been!
Yu, I—
All right you two, that's enough.
Yu-chan, I'm not sure that's very fair.
You lost the match, remember?
Kureha-san, I can't go!
Please, give us one more chance!
Nope, sorry.
I only gave you the first chance
for Hibari-kun's sake.
Besides, aren't you two
forgetting something?
Himari-chan has a debt to pay.
First thing's first, she should—
Then allow me to pay that off!
Here you go!
Wh-What's going on?
Ouch...
What's all this about?
Shii-kun, you're late.
Well it was a lot of cash.
Though, I will say,
hats off to that perfectionist
for making it in time.
Onii-chan!
Shinji-kun, you better explain yourself.
Like I said, I'm paying off
Himari-chan's debt on her behalf.
As an outsider, I can sign a contract
with Hibari-san to borrow money.
I didn't expect you
to betray me of all people.
Betray you? Please. You declined my offer.
Did you expect me to sit idly by?
You can't be that naive.
Well? You've got your money.
Any other problems?
I—
I'm over this!
Huh? Wait, um...
Thanks for ruining everything.
Hey now! Kureha-kun!
Stop that!
Hurry up and take me somewhere
cool so I can let you have it!
It's always this with you!
That's that. You can go now.
Bye-bye!
Are we off the hook?
I dunno, maybe?
According to Kureha-san, it was a loan.
Pay it off and it's a done deal.
Good thing I bought Natsu, Himari-chan,
and Rin-chan's entire high school years!
From now on, no quitting school
or going to Tokyo.
I won't allow it!
Of course, you'll also be forced
to make accessories until we graduate.
Stay tuned for other arrangements to follow.
Makishima-kun, you really are the worst.
I like to keep myself amused.
You three's rom-com does the trick.
Nothing wrong with paying
for a little entertainment.
Never mind that.
Now that things are settled, let's go out.
It'll be on Himari-chan, obviously.
Why would I be paying?!
Who do you have to thank but me?
You can't argue with me ever again!
Can you believe this guy, Enocchi?
Actually, sushi sounds great right now.
I see how it is!
I got bailed out but
definitely paid the price.
You gotta admit though, it was a huge help.
You're so soft on Makishima-kun.
You'll end up in trouble
if you keep hanging out with him.
I'd say that's already happened a few times.
See? You don't sense danger very well.
That's why your store will need me!
Oh yeah, about that...
I'm thinking of abandoning that dream.
What?! Why? Why?!
It's not like Kureha-san's stopping us!
Sorry, I worded that wrong.
I meant we still have the same root problem.
About what Sakura-san said?
The "playground frozen in time," was it?
Yup.
The main issue was my
stance towards customers.
That's on me, too.
No, I was the one being spoiled.
Saku-nee-san was trying
to tell me that all along.
I just wasn't listening to her.
I've been thinking, and I see it now.
I was too fixated on opening my own store.
Are you saying that shouldn't be our dream?
No, that's not it.
Opening a store by the time we're thirty
was our dream in middle school.
But if we don't keep an open mind,
we end up limiting ourselves.
Being so focused on that one dream
made me overlook the important things.
Like how I wanted to keep flowers
from dying back in grade school.
Or how I wanted to share
the beauty I saw in flowers with others.
Saku-nee-san was upset that I forgot
why I started in the first place.
I'm dreaming even bigger from now on.
Opening a store is only part of the process.
Love, my dreams, my own store...
Maybe it's selfish to want everything.
But I'll become someone worthy of it all.
From now on, I'll work harder
than Saku-nee-san.
I'll make sure Kureha-san
never looks down on me.
I won't give Hibari-san any reason to worry.
You'll never have to
sacrifice yourself again.
I promise to stand on my own two feet.
So...
It's not enough to have you
until I open a store.
Will you let me be selfish
and stand by me forever?
Y-You're making me blush.
Bwa-ha!
Hey, Yu! You idiot!
Found your weakness!
It's straightforward confessions!
Don't tease me like that!
I'm an emotional mess right now!
Stop playing it cool!
Oh yeah, Himari.
You forgot this.
My best friend ring...
Does this mean we're
still only best friends?
A totally unique best
friend ring just for you.
Oh, right. I chickened out back then.
There's something I haven't
told you about this ring.
See this here? It's a purple tulip seed.
Yeah, and...?
You see, um...
signifies "eternal love"
We used to be best friends...
But now... we're not.
Himari!
You're late!
Sorry, I was up late last night
after my shift at the family store.
Thanks for covering for me.
Will you give me something in return?
Like what?
Yu, do you love me?
How much?
More than anything in the world?
M-More than anything in the world.
Himari...
Go on?
I love you.
Bwa-he-he.
What was that?
Did the "Bwa-ha!" just evolve?
Must be the lovey-dovey version.
Himari's the cutest girl in the world
when she doesn't hide her feelings.
Good grief.
Getting it on early today, are we?
Yu-kun, Hii-chan, good morning.
M-Morning, Enomoto-san!
You two aren't plotting
to take Yu again, are you?!
He's mine!
I won't give you these with that attitude.
Here you go, Yu-kun.
Thanks!
Not fair! I want some too!
Sometimes, I get to thinking.
How we'll probably end up
in a similar spot.
We'll pretend to understand
each other even though we don't.
Even when we know
to put our desires into words,
our pride will sometimes get in the way.
Still, we'll push forward into the future.
This is our summer playground.
It's not over yet.